Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
- Correspondence
  - 1926
    - Nash, A. Company, The (Box 10)
    - National, Association - Winter (Box 10)
    - Naturalization, Aid - League (Box 10)
    - Nea - Nei (Box 10)
    - New Process Comoanv (Box 10)
    - New York Amsterdam News, The (Box 10)
    - New York City Board of Education (Box 10)
    - New York Evening Graphic (Box 10)
    - New York City Mission Society (Box 10)
    - New York State Department of Labor (Box 10)
    - New York University (Box 10)
    - Nich - Nick (Box 10)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 10)
    - Nye, Gerald P., Senator (Box 10)
    - Ortoluno, Nick (Box 10)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 10)
    - Par - Pat (Box 10)
    - Pea - Pet (Box 10)
    - Phelps, Mary (Box 10)
    - Pillsbury, George (Box 10)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 10)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 10)
      - Board of National Missions, 3 folders (Box 10)
      - General Council (Box 10)
      - Synod of New York (Box 10)
    - Presbyterian Magazine, The (Box 10)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Merle-Smith, Treasurer (Box 10)
        - Savage, Theodore F., Secretary, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk (Box 10)
      - Ruling Elders' Association (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Presbytery of Rochester, Executive Council (Box 10)
    - Provincetown Playhouse (Box 10)
    - Quil - Quin (Box 10)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 10)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 10)
    - Rel - Ret (Box 10)
    - Richards, Edward (Box 10)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 10)
    - Rick - Riv (Box 10)
    - Roc - Roy (Box 10)
    - Rutgers Presbyterian Church (Box 10)
    - Samson, Leon (Box 10)
    - Sche - Schi (Box 10)
    - Schneider, Charles A. (Box 10)
    - Seaboard Coke Company (Box 10)
    - Sheetz, Leroy (Box 10)
    - Simons, Minot (Box 10)
    - Social - Sociali (Box 10)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 10)
    - Springer, C. L. (Box 10)
    - Squires, Lester (Box 10)
    - Stauer, A. (Box 10)
    - Stelzle, Charles (Box 10)
    - Stew - Sto (Box 10)
    - Straton, John Roach (Box 10)
    - Stro - Stu (Box 10)
    - Talbott, George (Box 10)
    - Teachers' Union, The (Box 10)
    - Theta (Box 11)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 11)
    - Tra - Tru (Box 11)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 11)
    - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Incorporated, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - United States Civil - Department of Commerce (Box 11)
    - University of Michigan (Box 11)
    - Vanc - Van D (Box 11)
    - Vermont Realty Company, Incorporated (Box 11)
    - Viking Press, Incorporated, The (Box 11)
    - Waid, D. Everett (Box 11)
    - Wait - Wal (Box 11)
    - Wei - Wes (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Edna-Eleanor (Box 11)
    - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 11)
    - Wom - Wor (Box 11)
    - Wronker, Louis J., Alderman from Eighth District, City of New York (Box 11)
    - Young, Dr. (Box 11)
    - Y.M.C.A. (Box 11)
    - Y.W.C.A., 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Ziegler, Vinton (Box 11)
    - Unidentified (Box 11)
  - 1927
    - "Action" (Box 11)
    - Allen, Florence E. - Judge in Supreme Court of Ohio (Box 11)
    - American Association of Adult - Social Workers (Box 11)
    - American Birth Control League (Box 11)
    - American Civil - Worker (Box 11)
    - Asg - Assoc (Box 11)
    - Baird, Dr. Addison W. (Box 11)
    - Barr - Barru (Box 11)
    - Bashford, J. C. (Box 11)
    - Battle, George Gordon (Box 11)
    - Bea - Bech (Box 11)
    - Beck. G. F., 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Beine, Deborah (Box 11)
    - Ben - Bet (Box 11)
    - Bird - Birm (Box 11)
    - Blair, W. D. (Box 11)
    - Blanshard, Paul (Box 11)
    - Blans - Blu (Box 11)
    - Bor - Bow (Box 11)
    - Broo - Brow (Box 11)
    - Burrelle Press Clippings (Box 11)
    - Buttrey, A. J. (Box 11)
    - Cadman, S. Parkes (Box 11)
    - Came - Camp (Box 11)
    - Car - Cay (Box 11)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 8 folders (Box 11)
    - Chamberlain, Roy (Box 11)
    - Chap - Char (Box 11)
    - Chas - Chic (Box 11)
    - Christian-Jewish Fellowship (Box 11)
    - Christian Century, The (Box 11)
    - Church and Drama Association (Box 11)
    - Cit - Civ (Box 11)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 11)
    - Cole - Colo (Box 11)
    - Columbia University (Box 11)
    - Com - Conf (Box 11)
    - Cong - Cou (Box 11)
    - Cushier, Carrie (Box 11)
    - Dai - Dan (Box 11)
    - Darr - Dart (Box 11)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 11)
    - Davis & Sandt (Box 11)
    - Day Family (Box 11)
    - Debs - Deut (Box 12)
    - Dilles, Bertha (Box 12)
    - Dod - Doy (Box 12)
    - Durant, Will, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - East - Eastm S. (Box 12)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 12)
    - Emergency Committee for Strikers' Relief (Box 12)
    - Emergency Committee for Chinese Self-Government (Box 12)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica (Box 12)
    - Erickson, John A. (Box 12)
    - Esperanto Institute (Box 12)
    - Everett, Mrs. Edward (Box 12)
    - Fam - Far (Box 12)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Federated - Federation of A (Box 12)
    - Feiker, Mabel (Box 12)
    - Fellowship for a Christian Social Order (Box 12)
    - Fellowship of Faiths, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Fif - Fin (Box 12)
    - Flanagan, John (Box 12)
    - Fon - For (Box 12)
    - Franc - Frank (Box 12)
    - Free - Fren (Box 12)
    - Friends Seminary, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Gannett, Lewis (Box 12)
    - General Relief Committee, Textile Strikers (Box 12)
    - Gib - Gil (Box 12)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 12)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches (Box 12)
    - Griswold, Dorothy (Box 12)
    - Gundlach Advertising Company (Box 12)
    - Hal - Han (Box 12)
    - Har - Hat (Box 12)
    - Heck - Herm (Box 12)
    - Hill, Clifford (Box 12)
    - Hillman, Sidney (Box 12)
    - Hillquit, Morris (Box 12)
    - Holly, Michigan (Box 12)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 12)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 12)
    - Home Life - News (Box 12)
    - Hopkins, J. H. (Box 12)
    - Hor - How (Box 12)
    - Hud - Hut (Box 12)
    - Imrie, Gordon (Box 12)
    - Ind - Inq (Box 12)
    - International - Inwood (Box 12)
    - Jelliffe, Reverend W. R. (Box 12)
    - Jewish Social Service Association (Box 12)
    - Journal of the National Educational Association (Box 12)
    - Kaneda, Kazno (Box 12)
    - Kee - Kel (Box 12)
    - Kips Bay Neighbor (Box 12)
    - Knight, Walter D. (Box 12)
    - Kuger, Alfred A. (Box 12)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 12)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello (congressman) (Box 12)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmation, Notices of Church Services, Replies (Box 12)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses Arranged for (Box 12)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes (Box 12)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 8 folders (Box 12)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment, etc., 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Programs and Activities January-September (Box 12)
      - Programs and Activities October-December (Box 13)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 13)
      - Work Schedule and Instructions to Personnel, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Lan - Lau (Box 13)
    - League for, I to A (Box 13)
    - Leig - Levy (Box 13)
    - Lindb - Linde (Box 13)
    - Lord's Day Alliance of the United States (Box 13)
    - Lyon, A. - W. H. (Box 13)
    - MacCracken, Mrs. H. N. (Box 13)
    - Mach - Man (Box 13)
    - Massachusetts, Office of the Governor, Fuller, Alvan T. (Box 13)
    - McC - McK (Box 13)
    - Mead, Vern S. (Box 13)
    - Merr - Met (Box 13)
    - Mic - Min (Box 13)
    - Mof - Mothers A (Box 13)
    - Mothersill, Mark (Box 13)
    - Mothersill, Roland (Box 13)
    - Motin, Reverend Nicholas (Box 13)
    - Muste, A. J., 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Nation, The (Box 13)
    - National Bureau-Committee (Box 13)
    - National, Con - Cou (Box 13)
    - National, S - W (Box 13)
    - Near East Relief (Box 13)
    - New York City
      - Government and Departments of (Box 13)
      - Hospitals (Box 13)
      - Mission Society (Box 13)
      - Newspapers (Box 13)
    - New York University (Box 13)
    - Newman, Wilson L. (Box 13)
    - Nickless, Reverend Alfred L. (Box 13)
    - Nicola, C. Blanche (Box 13)
    - Noble, Daniel R. (Box 13)
    - Nolting, Edward L., 2 folders (Box 13)
    - O'Brien, Daniel (Box 13)
    - Occomy, Katherine (Box 13)
    - Oquossoc Union Parish (Box 13)
    - Outlook, The (Box 13)
    - Overstreet, Harry A. (Box 13)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 13)
    - Par - Pau (Box 13)
    - Pe - Pi (Box 13)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 13)
    - Plai - Play (Box 13)
    - Pol - Powe (Box 13)
    - Powys, John Cowper (Box 13)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 13)
      - Board of Ministerial Relief and Sustenation (Box 13)
      - Board of National Missions, 4 folders (Box 13)
      - General Assembly's Committee on Temperance (Box 13)
      - Synod of New York (Box 13)
    - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box 13)
    - Presbytery of Brooklyn - Nassau, Church Extension Board (Box 13)
    - Presbytery of New York, Church Extension Committee
      - Merle-Smith, Treasurer (Box 13)
      - Savage, Theodore F., Secretary, 3 folders (Box 13)
      - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk (Box 13)
    - Protestant Brotherhood (Box 13)
    - Pulaski, Mrs. (Box 13)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 13)
    - Quinlan, Florence (Box 13)
    - Rand School of Social Science, The (Box 13)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 13)
    - Rea - Rei (Box 13)
    - Richards, Edward (Box 13)
    - Richards, George (Box 13)
    - Ric - Riv (Box 13)
    - Roc - Ros (Box 13)
    - Roth, Emery (Box 13)
    - Sacc - Saks (Box 13)
    - Schiff, Jacob H. Center, The Sisterhood of (Box 13)
    - Scife, Josephine (Box 13)
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln (Box 13)
    - Schwa - Schwi (Box 13)
    - Searle, Miss A. C. (Box 13)
    - Sha - Sho (Box 13)
    - Somerville, John (Box 14)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Spi - Spr (Box 14)
    - Sta - Stel (Box 14)
    - Stewart, Reverend George, Jr. (Box 14)
    - Stone, Dr. Abraham (Box 14)
    - Str - Stu (Box 14)
    - Sun - Sur (Box 14)
    - Tal - Tay (Box 14)
    - Teacher's Union, The (City of New York) (Box 14)
    - The - Thomas, M. (Box 14)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 14)
    - Thorne, Mary E. (Box 14)
    - Tibbits, J. H. (Box 14)
    - Totah, Ermina Jones (Box 14)
    - Trade Union Delegation to Europe (Box 14)
    - Tucker, Mrs. Christine Wilson (Box 14)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 14)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - United Textile Workers of America (Box 14)
    - Veillierre, Mae (Box 14)
    - Vic - Vin (Box 14)
    - Waid, D. Everett (Box 14)
    - Wal - Wan (Box 14)
    - Web - Wei (Box 14)
    - Welfare Council of New York City, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Wel - Wes (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, Burton K., Senator, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, C. - Whi (Box 14)
    - Wilb - Will (Box 14)
    - Wise, James W. (Box 14)
    - Wise, Stephen S., 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Women's Press, The (Box 14)
    - Worker's Education Bureau (Box 14)
    - Workman's Education Association (Box 14)
    - World Alliances (Box 14)
    - Wright, Mary (Box 14)
    - X A (Box 14)
    - Yergin, Howard (Box 14)
    - Young, J. Lowe (Box 14)
    - Y.M.C.A., 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Y.W.C.A., 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Zic - Zit (Box 14)
    - Unidentified (Box 14)
  - 1928
    - "Action" (Clement Schwinges) (Box 14)
    - Albarino, Sam (Box 14)
    - All-America Anti-Imperialist League (Box 14)
    - Allison, Milton Myers (Box 14)
    - Amalgamated B - S (Box 14)
    - American Association for Adult Education (Box 14)
    - American Association for Labor - OAS (Box 14)
    - American Bi - Bo (Box 14)
    - American C - X-Ray (includes X-Rays of Chaffee's teeth) (Box 14)
    - Ana - And (Box 14)
    - Arnold Constable (Box 14)
    - Artist's Council for Prison Service, The (Box 14)
    - Association for the Welfare of the Children of China (Box 14)
    - Atlas Social Service Exchange, Incorporated (Box 14)
    - Bag - Bail (Box 14)
    - Baird, Dr. Addison W. (Box 14)
    - Ball - Bait (Box 14)
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer (Box 14)
    - Barr - Barro (Box 14)
    - Barrus, George L. (Box 14)
    - Baumes, Caleb H., New York State Senator (Box 14)
    - Beck, G. F., 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Bel - Bet (Box 14)
    - Berman, Max (Box 14)
    - Birmingham Public - T. W. (Box 14)
    - Bre - Bru (Box 14)
    - Bug - But (Box 14)
    - Cadman, S. Parkes (Box 14)
    - Cal - Cap (Box 14)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 14)
    - Cavert, Samuel McCrae (Box 14)
    - Central Trades and Labor Council (Box 14)
    - Cercle Victor Hugo, Le (Box 14)
    - Chaffee, Professor Zacharia (Box 14)
    - Chaffee, Family of January-June, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Chaffee, Family of July-December, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Cham - Chu (Box 15)
    - Civic Club, The (Box 15)
    - Clergy Club of New York and Neighborhood, The (Box 15)
    - Coffey, Gertrude (Box 15)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 15)
    - Cog - Col (Box 15)
    - Com - Con (Box 15)
    - Cool - Coop (Box 15)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 15)
    - Craig, Francis (Box 15)
    - Crain, Thomas C. T., Justice in the Supreme Court of the State of New York (Box 15)
    - Cre - Cro (Box 15)
    - Cusimano, Mary M. (Box 15)
    - Damrosch, Mrs. Walter (Box 15)
    - Darling, George A. (Box 15)
    - Dartmouth Christian Association (Box 15)
    - Davis, Jerome, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Day, Stanley (Box 15)
    - Dea - Denn (Box 15)
    - Doerfler, L. (Box 15)
    - Duffield, Reverend Howard (Box 15)
    - Durant, Will (Box 15)
    - East - Eastm S. (Box 15)
    - Emanuel Sisterhood of Personal Service (Box 15)
    - Emergency Committee for Striker's Relief (Box 15)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica (Box 15)
    - Equitable Trust Company of New York (Box 15)
    - Esmond, Burton D., Assemblyman (Box 15)
    - Evangelical Trumpeters, The (Box 15)
    - Everett, Mrs. (Box 15)
    - Fam - Far (Box 15)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Fellowship of Faiths, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Ferris, Gilbert B. (Box 15)
    - Fie - Fit (Box 15)
    - Flagler, Harry Harkness (Box 15)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 15)
    - Ford - Fore (Box 15)
    - Frence - French (Box 15)
    - Friendly Lodge for Blind Girls (Box 15)
    - Friends Seminary (Box 15)
    - Friendship Center (Box 15)
    - Ful - Fun (Box 15)
    - Gal - Gar (Box 15)
    - Gen - Ger (Box 15)
    - Gilfillian, S. Columb (Box 15)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 15)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches (Box 15)
    - Green, William, President of the American Federation of Labor (Box 15)
    - Hab - Hal (Box 15)
    - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 15)
    - Harr - Hat (Box 15)
    - Hays, Arthur Garfield (Box 15)
    - Hays, Theodore (Box 15)
    - Hea - Hes (Box 15)
    - Hill ... (Box 15)
    - Hoa - Holl (Box 15)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 15)
    - Hoo - Hou (Box 15)
    - Hud - Hut (Box 15)
    - Ime - Imp (Box 15)
    - Independent Committee for Thomas (Norman) for President (Box 15)
    - Inter-Group Bureau of Social Education (Box 15)
    - International, House - Pocketworkers (Box 15)
    - Iowa State Traveling Men's Association (Box 15)
    - Japanese-Christian Association (Box 15)
    - Jel - Jen (Box 15)
    - Jones, Thomas E., President of Fisk University (Box 15)
    - Kei - Kel (Box 15)
    - Kil - Kin (Box 15)
    - Knight, Reverend Walter D. (Box 15)
    - Kristnapp, S. S. (Box 15)
    - Kugel, Alfred (Box 15)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 15)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello, Congressman (Box 15)
    - Labor Defender, The (Box 15)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services, Responses (Box 16)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 16)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 4 folders (Box 16)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arrangements for, 3 folders (Box 16)
      - Contributions to Labor Temple, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 5 folders (Box 16)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 3 folders (Box 16)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment, 3 folders (Box 16)
      - Programs and Activities, 10 folders (Box 16)
      - Solicitations for Labor Temple Business (Box 16)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 4 folders (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Lai - Lav (Box 16)
    - League, Abolish - Industrial (Box 16)
    - Lee, Ivy (Box 16)
    - Leiper, H. S. (Box 16)
    - Lenox Hill Association (Box 16)
    - Levine, Isaac Don (Box 16)
    - Lewis, R. E. (Box 16)
    - Lib - Lis (Box 16)
    - Lor - Low (Box 16)
    - Lucille LaVerne Theatre (Box 16)
    - Lyn - Lyons (Box 16)
    - Mac - Man (Box 16)
    - Mar - May (Box 16)
    - McConnell, Francis J. (Box 16)
    - McCr - McM (Box 16)
    - Melendy, Emery A. (Box 16)
    - Met - Mey (Box 16)
    - Mil - Mini (Box 16)
    - Mod - Mon (Box 16)
    - Muniz, Manuel (Box 16)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 16)
    - Myers, James (Box 16)
    - Nar - National C (Box 16)
    - National Geographic Society (Box 16)
    - National, R - V (Box 16)
    - Nea - New M. (Box 16)
    - New York, City of (Box 16)
    - New York City Mission Society (Box 16)
    - New York Department of Education, Special Schools Bureau, Hague, John B., chief (Box 16)
    - New York, E - Sk (Box 16)
    - New York, T - U (Box 16)
    - Newell, Frederick (Box 16)
    - Nicola, Blanche (Box 16)
    - Nieubuhr, Reinhold (Box 16)
    - Noble, H. W. (Box 16)
    - Nolting, Edward (Box 16)
    - Nye, Senator Gerlad P. (Box 17)
    - Open Forum Speakers' Bureau (Box 17)
    - Ortolono, Nicholas (Box 17)
    - Osborne, Agnes Wilson (Box 17)
    - Outlook, The, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Overstreet, Harry A. (Box 17)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 17)
    - Pai - Pax (Box 17)
    - Perkins, Margaret (Box 17)
    - Pierson, Anna (Box 17)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 17)
    - Pond, James B. (Box 17)
    - Presbyterian Board of Ministerial Relief and Sustenation (Box 17)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 17)
      - Board of National Missions, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Board of Pensions (Box 17)
      - Office of the Moderator (Box 17)
    - Presbyterian Ministers Fund for Life Insurance (Box 17)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 17)
    - Presbytery of Chicago, Church Extension Board (Box 17)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Merle-Smith, Treasurer, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Savage, Theodore F., Secretary, 3 folders (Box 17)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 17)
      - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Youth of New York Presbytery (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Pub - Put (Box 17)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 17)
    - Rao - Rau (Box 17)
    - Rec - Rep (Box 17)
    - Richards, Edward C. M. (Box 17)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 17)
    - Rivenberg, Harold (Box 17)
    - Rog - Rot (Box 17)
    - Rus - Rutg (Box 17)
    - Sal - Say (Box 17)
    - Schmalhausen, Samuel D., 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Schneider, Mrs. A. F. (Box 17)
    - Sea - Sem (Box 17)
    - Sha - Shi (Box 17)
    - Sill, Alfreda P. (Box 17)
    - Silver, Alfred A. (Box 17)
    - Smith College (Box 17)
    - Social S - Socialist P (Box 17)
    - Sod - Son (Box 17)
    - Spea - Speer (Box 17)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Spi - Spr (Box 17)
    - Stei - Stew (Box 17)
    - Stone, Drs. Abraham and Hannah (Box 17)
    - Stra - Stro (Box 17)
    - Survey Graphic (Box 17)
    - Telephone Message Bureau (Box 17)
    - Thes - Thet (Box 17)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 17)
    - Thomas Testimonial Dinner Committee (Box 17)
    - Tib - Tip (Box 17)
    - Tron, Bartholemew (Box 17)
    - Tucker, Mrs. W. Ellsworth (Box 17)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - United Neighborhood Houses (Box 17)
    - United States Departments of Government (Box 17)
    - Universal Religious Peace Conference (Box 17)
    - Vac - Vande (Box 17)
    - Van Dy - Van T (Box 17)
    - Vermont, State of, re: buying a summer home (Box 17)
    - Vineyard Shore Workers’ School (Box 17)
    - Voc - Von (Box 17)
    - Wagner, C. Everett (Box 17)
    - Wagner, Robert F., Senator (Box 17)
    - Waid, B. E. (Box 17)
    - Waid, D. Everett (Box 17)
    - Walker, J. E. (Box 17)
    - Walker, James J., Mayor, New York City (Box 17)
    - Wal - Wat (Box 17)
    - Webber, Charles C. (Box 17)
    - Welfare Council of New York City (Box 18)
    - Welg - Wes (Box 18)
    - Wheeler, Burton K., Senator (Box 18)
    - White - Whiton (Box 18)
    - Wiesenberg, Mrs. C. (Box 18)
    - Wise, James and Stephen S. (Box 18)
    - Woll, Matthew (Box 18)
    - Wom - World (Box 18)
    - World A - T (Box 18)
    - Wronker, L. J., Alderman, New York City (Box 18)
    - Yale Graduate Placement Bureau (Box 18)
    - Yergin, Howard (Box 18)
    - Young, Dr. J. Lowe (Box 18)
    - Y.M.C.A., 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Y.W.C.A. (Box 18)
    - Unidentified (Box 18)
  - 1929
    - Abbe - Abr (Box 18)
    - "Action" (Box 18)
    - Affiliated Baptist City Societies (Box 18)
    - Airolite Company, The (Box 18)
    - Alb - All (Box 18)
    - American Ar - As (Box 18)
    - American B - F (Box 18)
    - American L - R (Box 18)
    - American Society for the Control of Cancer (Box 18)
    - American Se - Soc (Box 18)
    - American T - America's (Box 18)
    - Anookulam, James J. (Box 18)
    - Arbitrator, The (Box 18)
    - Arnold Constable and Company (Box 18)
    - Ashley, Miss Mildred (Box 18)
    - Baj - Bak (Box 18)
    - Balfour, Mary (Box 18)
    - Bali - Barb (Box 18)
    - Barn - Barr (Box 18)
    - Barru - Bau (Box 18)
    - Beck, G. F., 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Bel - Ben (Box 18)
    - Ber - Bet (Box 18)
    - Bib - Big (Box 18)
    - Bloom, Sara (Box 18)
    - Bon - Boy (Box 18)
    - Bre - Bro (Box 18)
    - Bur - But (Box 18)
    - Camps... (Box 18)
    - Campb - Car (Box 18)
    - Central Needle Trades School and Evening School (Box 18)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Char - Chu (Box 18)
    - Citi - City (Box 18)
    - Clarke, Merril Fowler (Box 18)
    - Cle - Cli (Box 18)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 18)
    - Cohen, E - G (Box 18)
    - Coleman, McAllister (Box 18)
    - Collins, Ross A., Congressman (Box 18)
    - Columbia Book Company (Box 18)
    - Columbia University (Box 18)
    - Com - Coo (Box 18)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 18)
    - Cou - Cox (Box 18)
    - Cra - Cro (Box 18)
    - Cusimano, Mary (Box 18)
    - Daidone (Box 18)
    - Damrosch, Mrs. Walter (Box 18)
    - Dartmouth Christian Association (Box 18)
    - Daublin, Benjamin (Box 18)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 18)
    - Dend - Denn (Box 18)
    - Dod - Dou (Box 18)
    - Downing, Bernard, New York State Senator (Box 18)
    - Dress Manufacturers' Protective Association (Box 18)
    - Durant, Will (Box 18)
    - Dutton, E. P., and Company (Box 18)
    - Eastern Clergy Bureau (Box 18)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 18)
    - Edge, Reverend James (Box 18)
    - Elliot, James H. (Box 18)
    - Emmerich Bureau (Box 19)
    - Epworth Herald, The (Box 19)
    - Equitist, The (Box 19)
    - Estill, Reul (Box 19)
    - Evang - Evans (Box 19)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Federation F - O (Box 19)
    - Feldman, Mrs. (Box 19)
    - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 19)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 19)